Library of Congress and Fisk University Mississippi Delta collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Sound Recordings, 97 sound discs
  - AFS 06664, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by four girls and recorded by Alan Lomax in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. I Heard the Voice of Jesus Say, 1942
      - 2. All My Trouble Will Be Over After While, 1942
    - Side B
      - All Power is in His Hands, 1942
  - AFS 06665, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax in Clarksdale, Mississippi; performer unidentified.
    - Side A
      - 1. Good Old Man, 1942
      - 2. Satisfy, 1942
      - 3. Satisfy, 1942
      - 4. Satisfy, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Go In and Out the Window, 1942
      - 2. Jump for Joy, 1942
      - 3. Tip-a-gho, 1942
      - 4. Tip-a-gho, 1942
      - 5. Old Georgia Rabbit, 1942
      - 6. It Ain't Goin' Rain No Mo', 1942
  - AFS 06666, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06666a
      - 1. It Ain't Goin' Rain No Mo', 1942
      - 2. Sally Pick a Susy, 1942
      - 3. You Got to Take Sick and Die Some of These Days, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Why Don't Live So God Can Use You, 1942
      - 2. Country Blues, 1942
  - AFS 06667, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. You Gonna Miss Me When I'm Dead And Gone, 1942
      - 2. Levee Camp Blues, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Levee Camp Blues, 1942
      - 2. 32-20 Blues, 1942
  - AFS 06668, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax in Lula, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Rock Me, Shake Me, 1942
        Performed by Manuel Casey.
      - 2. Witness for the Lord, 1942
        Performed by Mrs. Roxie Threadgill.
      - 3. I'm Gon' Lean on the Lord, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Done Taken My Lord Away, 1942
        Performed by Mary Lee Johnson.
      - 2. Rock, Daniel, 1942
      - 3. Shout for Joy, 1942
      - 4. You Got to Stand Your Test in Judgement, 1942
      - 5. Low Down Your Chariot and Let Me Ride, 1942
      - 6. Father, I Stretch My Hand To Thee, 1942
  - AFS 06669, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A Track 1 recorded by Alan Lomax in Lula, Mississippi. Side A Tracks 2-6 and Side B recorded by Alan Lomax in Dundee, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Sorry, Sorry to Leave You, 1942
        Performed by Mrs. Roxie Threadgill and Mary Lee Johnson.
      - 2. Red Wasp is Stinging Me, 1942
        Performed by Etherene Harris.
      - 3. Who de Cat, 1942
      - 4. Miss Sue from Alabama, 1942
      - 5. Draw a Bucket of Water, 1942
      - 6. Edimo Rocka, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Gwan Down, Rabbit, 1942
      - 2. Gwan Down, Rabbit, 1942
        Performed by Anne Williams.
      - 3. Satisfy, 1942
      - 4. Sea Lion, 1942
  - AFS 06670, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax in Dundee, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06670a
      - 1. The Eighth of January, 1942
        Performed by Sidney Hemphill, Lucious Smith, Alec Askew, and Will Head.
      - 2. Interview with Sidney Hemphill, 1942
      - 3. Interview with Sidney Hemphill, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06670b
      - 1. The Carrier Railroad, 1942
        Performed by Sidney Hemphill.
      - 2. The Roguish Man, 1942
  - AFS 06671, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06671a
      - 1. The Strayhorn Mob, 1942
      - 2. The Boll Weevil, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06671b
      - The Arkansas Traveler, 1942
  - AFS 06672, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06672a
      - 1. Emmaline, Take Yo' Time, 1942
        Performed by Alec Askew on 4-hole quill.
      - 2. Tuning of four-hole quills, 1942
      - 3. Emmaline, Take Yo' Time, 1942
      - 4. Emmaline, Take Yo' Time, 1942
        Performed by Sidney Hemphill on 10-hole quill.
      - 5. The Devil's Dream, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06672b
      - 1. Test, 1942
      - 2. Leather Britches, 1942
      - 3. Rice Straw, 1942
      - 4. So Soon I'll Be At Home, 1942
      - 5. Old Blue, 1942
  - AFS 00673, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Sidney Hemphill and recorded by Alan Lomax in Dundee, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06673a
      - 1. Jesse James, 1942
        With fife.
      - 2. After the Ball is Over, 1942
      - 3. The Sidewalks of New York, 1942
      - 4. The Death March, 1942
      - 5. Test, 1942
      - 6. John Henry, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06673b
      - 1. Keep My Skillet Greasy, If I Can, 1942
        With violin.
      - 2. Hog Hunt, 1942
      - 3. Soon in the Mornin', 1942
        With banjo.